<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chimu Homeopathy</title>
    <description>David S. Kim is a homeopath.</description>
    <link>http://chimuhomeopathy.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://chimuhomeopathy.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 23:58:20 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 23:58:20 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Note on Healing Justice</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have a deep faith in homeopathy. I love its endlessness, its mystery, its breathtaking power. But as a tradition, it is not without cracks. Many of the early (male) leaders of homeopathy pathologized gender nonconformity, non-hetero sexualities, and women. Many of our old texts reflect this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And while homeopathy was birthed in Germany, it draws on the knowledge of peoples and places around the world. Some of this knowledge was gathered justly from German traditions; some was given freely; some was taken within the context of slavery, colonialism and genocide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Healing justice, like homeopathy, is about freedom. Freedom to dream, to mourn, to love, to be, to connect, to wonder, to live, to create, to move. Freedom that renders oppression redundant—that reveals capitalism, white supremacy, colonialism and patriarchy as weak in the face of our collective Vital Force.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Healing justice is centering women, queer and trans folks, people of Color, Indigenous peoples. For me, healing justice and homeopathy, in relationship, bring each other to greater potency.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://chimuhomeopathy.com/blog/a-note-on-healing-justice</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://chimuhomeopathy.com/blog/a-note-on-healing-justice</guid>
        
        <category>Homeopathy, Healing Justice</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
